musicboxnewtab.com 2015-12-29

# 

MusicBox, a product distributed to INMIND INC., ("MusicBox") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about MusicBox's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how MusicBox receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the imusicnewtab.com website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site").

Collection and Use of Information

MusicBox does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information").

MusicBox may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on MusicBox's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. MusicBox's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

MusicBox may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. MusicBox collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. MusicBox will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

MusicBox does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. MusicBox may disclose your Personal Information if MusicBox believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on MusicBox (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MusicBox (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MusicBox services or members of the public.

Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the MusicBox website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that MusicBox shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. MusicBox shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable.

Security

MusicBox takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although MusicBox cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, MusicBox has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

Changes to Policy

From time to time, MusicBox may revise this Policy. MusicBox will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information MusicBox collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

Change or Removal of Information

If a user's e-mail address changes or you wish you remove your e-mail address, you can contact us at: support@imusicnewtab.com with the request or by contacting us at the contact information listed below.

Contact Information

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to [privacy@imusicnewtab.com](mailto:privacy@imusicnewtab.com) or by writing to MusicBox, Attention: Privacy Policy Officer, 40 Kimonos St. 3095, Limassol, Cyprus.
